Karan Kumar Aneja R

Detail-oriented, analytical, and self-driven programmer with extensive experience building user-facing applications. Efficient and knowledgeable coder with skills in HTML, CSS and JavaScript programming languages. Coordinated and collaborative team player with attention to detail and ability to contribute to code base improvement initiatives and UX improvement projects.

©:+91-9980672016

karananeja.r@gmail.com
igithub.com/karananeja
in : linkedin.com/in/aneja07
leetcode.com/karananeja

EXPERIENCE

INTELLICAR TELEMATICS PRIVATE LIMITED, B'luru — Frontend Web Developer

JAN 2023 - PRESENT

- Working as Front End Developer.
- Developed Applications using React and TypeScript.
- o Collaborated with other Team members and Stakeholders.
- Used Git and GitHub to maintain and manage the code base.
- Used Axios to Integrate the Back End to the Front End.

SPIN GAMES INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED, Chennai — *Game Developer*

FEB 2022 - JAN 2023

- o Worked as Front End Engineer.
- Developed Slot Games using Phaser.js (JavaScript Framework).
- o Collaborated with other Team members and Stakeholders.
- Used SourceTree and Bitbucket to maintain and manage the code base.
- Used Ajax to Integrate the Back End to the Front End.

AMAZON DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED, B'luru — Investigation Specialist

NOV 2020 – FEB 2022

- o Worked as Risk Investigator, trained to assess risk in multiple marketplaces including US and CA.
- Worked on Multiple queues such Variations, LRM, Variation Appeals, Mutation Abuse and Mutation Abuse Appeals.
- o Helped Sellers in boosting their Sales and receiving more Orders based on their performance.
- o Prepared new SOP like guidelines PPT which can be used for training purpose.
- Investigated suspicious activities which could delude the Amazon Customers.

EDUCATION

$\textbf{NEW HORIZON COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING,} \ B'luru - \textit{Mechanical Engineering}$

JUL 2015 – SEP 2019, Board – Autonomous (affiliated to VTU), CGPA – 9.23

ST. JOSEPH'S PRE - UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, B'luru - XIIth Standard

JUN 2013 – MAY 2015, Board – KSEEB, Specialization – PCMB, Percentage – 87.83%

PROJECTS

Inventory Management System -

It is a system built modern technologies such as React, React Query and SASS for creating, managing and maintaining information regarding the Inventory of an Organization for both physical and virtual product.

Royal Fortunes Game -

It is a slot game built using Phaser.js and uses canvas element of HTML, it has Base Game and Free Game feature, it is a 9-reel concept with 3x3 matrix layout, where each symbol is a different reel and awards wins to the Player in multiple line win combination such as Vertical, Horizontal and Diagonal Lines.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, Phaser.js, Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Jira, SourceTree, React JS, Redux, Node JS, npm, express, Mongo DB, Firebase, Recoil, Echarts, Axios, React Query

ACHIEVEMENTS

6th rank in Mechanical Engineering.

First prize in TecHorizon 2019.

Completed 100 DaysOfCode – Learnt HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python.

CERTIFICATES

Responsive Web Design Certification – freeCodeCamp.

INTERESTS

Teaching, Biking, Trekking.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 31/07/97

Nationality: Indian

Address: Bengaluru

LANGUAGES KNOWN

English, Hindi, Kannada, and Punjabi